Guide to the Construction on Campus negatives, 1964-1968 UA 446
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Construction on Campus negatives
1964-1968
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Pitman, H. Russell
UA 446
.25 Linear Feet 1 document box
This collection includes 32 sleeves of 4" x 5" black and white photographic negatives of buildings and interiors of the Rice University campus taken in the 1960's.
Biographical / Historical
This collection includes 32 sleeves of 4" x 5" black and white photographic negatives of buildings and interiors of the Rice University campus taken in the 1960's. The negatives were rehoused when donated to the Woodson Research Center in 1992. Some of the work photographed was done by Linbeck Construction, and some by Tellepsen Construction.
Scope and Contents
This collection includes 32 sleeves of 4" x 5" black and white photographic negatives of buildings and interiors of the Rice University campus taken in the 1960's.
Conditions Governing Access
Stored onsite at the Woodson Research Center.
Restrictions on Access
This collection is open for research.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The negatives were donated to the Woodson Research Center in November 1992 by Russell Pitman, long-time Campus Business Affairs Manager.
Related Materials
Additional photographs and negatives of the Rice University campus can be found in the following Woodson Research Center collections:
Rice University Photograph Files, UA 363
Rice University News and Media Relations; Board, Administration and Faculty Photo and Research files, UA 187
Rice University Campus Photographer Files, UA 188
Separated Materials
One sleeve of photographs, envelope 31 of the Ryon Lab photos taken in July 1964, was discovered to be missing in February 2022.
Index Terms
Subjects
Rice University -- History; Universities and colleges
Document Types
negatives (photographic)
Subjects (Persons)
Pitman, H. Russell
- Series I: Construction on campus negatives
  - Rice Math Science Building, 1967-05-10 (Box 1, Envelope 1)
  - Rice Math Science Lab Tellepsen Construction, 1967-07-07 (Box 1, Envelope 2)
  - Rice Math Science Building Tellepsen Construction, 1967-09-07 (Box 1, Envelope 3)
  - Rice Math Science Building Tellepsen Construction, 1967-12-07 (Box 1, Envelope 4)
  - Rice Math Science Building Tellepsen Construction, 1968-04-11 (Box 1, Envelope 5)
  - Rice Math Science Building, 1968-06-12 (Box 1, Envelope 6)
  - Rice Math Science Building Tellepsen Constrcution, 1968-08-14 (Box 1, Envelope 7)
  - Rice Lab, 1965-06-02 (Box 1, Envelope 8)
  - Rice Math Lab, 1967-10-09 (Box 1, Envelope 9)
  - Rice Math Lab, 1967-11-08 (Box 1, Envelope 10)
  - Rice Math Lab, 1968-02-09 (Box 1, Envelope 11)
  - Rice Math Lab, 1968-03-14 (Box 1, Envelope 12)
  - Rice Research Lab, 1965-05-06 (Box 1, Envelope 13)
  - Rice Space Lab, 1965-12-07 (Box 1, Envelope 14)
  - Rice Space Lab, 1965-10-04 (Box 1, Envelope 15)
  - Space Science and Technology Lab, 1968-07-02 (Box 1, Envelope 16)
  - Space Science and Technology Lab, 1965-08-03 (Box 1, Envelope 17)
  - Space Science and Technology Lab, 1965-09-02 (Box 1, Envelope 18)
  - Space Science and Technology Lab, 1966-01-10 (Box 1, Envelope 19)
  - Space Science and Technology Lab, 1966-02-04 (Box 1, Envelope 20)
  - Space Science and Technology Lab, 1966-03-04 (Box 1, Envelope 21)
  - Space Science and Technology Lab, 1966-04-08 (Box 1, Envelope 22)
  - Space Science and Technology Lab, 1966-05-27 (Box 1, Envelope 23)
  - Space Science and Technology Lab, 1966-06-21 (Box 1, Envelope 24)
  - Space Science and Technology Lab, 1966-07-28 (Box 1, Envelope 25)
  - Space Science and Technology Lab, 1966-08-23 (Box 1, Envelope 26)
  - Space Science and Technology Lab, 1966-09-22 (Box 1, Envelope 27)
  - Space Science and Technology Lab, 1966-10-21 (Box 1, Envelope 28)
  - Space Science and Technology Lab, 1966-11-22 (Box 1, Envelope 29)
  - Ryon Lab, 1964-03-26 (Box 1, Envelope 30)
  - Rice Hotel Laundry, 1965-05-05 (Box 1, Envelope 32)
  - Rice Hotel Laundry, 1965-06-21 (Box 1, Envelope 33)